[{"answer": "my friend? What are you doing here", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Help me how", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "He met a girl", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Yeah", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It was good", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You asked if I was coming?  I mean...my plans got cancelled..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Come on. I don't believe that", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah. I like you. Of course I do", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah. I like you. Of course I do", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Right. As a friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "As a friend", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Just as a friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh yeah totally. Friends. You and me. That's... perfect", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Cool", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "The same girl you'd been whining and crying and bitching about for weeks now", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "The same girl you said was way out of your league and you'd have no chance with no matter what. That girl", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "That's what I love about him.  Ooh", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I know what you mean. That's what happened with me and my friend", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "My boyfriend before my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Holy shit you are. I can't believe you", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yeah. I'm all done", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Huh", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I am. I'm sorry for acting like a jerk", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What? Why", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Well... You don't want to just, maybe, go to dinner. I mean, you've gotta eat right", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You're not having any fun", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I'm dancing. I haven't danced in ages. God. Come on", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'm out of twinkies", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Go... where", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "It's playing at 5", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I don't know. You wanna maybe go back to your place or", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Now...I think I'm gonna call it a day", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I've got pasta at home", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What's different now? How could things change so quickly", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "What happened?! That's what I don't get", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "It would appear", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yes it is", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Hmm", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Grew up not too far from here. my friend, near that place", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes! Exactly. I totally agree", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You have? Really? Hmm. I didn't see you", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "500-Days-of-Summer.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 48}]